I'm freezing! I'm definitely
gonna wear a scarf tomorrow.
It gets pretty cold in the evenings now, huh.
Y-Yo.
Hey.
Hey, you! Don't you go
stealing my Miyamura, Tanihara!
I-I'm not stealing him from you, jeez!
You guys are so weird! You're always
cuddling with each other and stuff!
S-Sorry, but that's all it is!
We've kinda gotten close lately, that's it!
The hell do you mean, you've gotten close?
Closer than just friends?
Oh, please. I'm not Shindo.
Dude!
W-Wait, really? Is that
what Shindo-kun is to you?
"Creak..."
W-Wait, really? Is that
what Shindo-kun is to you?
"Trembling"
"Creak..."
W-Wait, really? Is that
what Shindo-kun is to you?
"Trembling"
W-Wait, really? Is that
what Shindo-kun is to you?
"Trembling"
Absolutely not!
C'mon, Tanihara, spill the damn beans!
I mean, I saw Shindo go over to
Miyamura's to get a change of clothes once.
Look, he stays over at my place a lot!
Even when I don't want him to!
A wild Shindo appears!
Why're you guys blockin' the
sidewalk? What's goin' on, huh?
Shindo-kun, are you close with Chika-chan?
Kinda? Though lately,
she's been busy studying for exams,
so we haven't hung out much.
Though I've spent plenty
of nights at Miyamura's!
"* Playing video games."
Though I've spent plenty
of nights at Miyamura's!
Hey, Shindo, let's go get some Mickey D's!
Can't spell "burger"
without Shindo, am I right?!
Wait, what? Makes no sense, but okay.
Is that free coffee coupon still good?
No, it expired.
Miyamura, I just want you
to know something, okay?
I'm not worried about girls.
But when I think about
some guy taking you, I can't...
Taking me how?!
Promise me this! If you fall for
someone else, it better be a girl!
No guys, okay?!
O-Okay!
So I had to promise her "no guys" yesterday.
You guys need to stay away from me, okay?!
Sure, but... what about when
you need to use the bathroom?
I just won't go!
Good luck with that, bro.
"Horimiya"
Man, this is my day off!
You could've gone shopping
for art supplies by yourself!
"Until the Snow Melts"
You could've gone shopping
for art supplies by yourself!
"Until the Snow Melts"
I want to hit up the bookstore, too.
I can't carry everything by myself.
"Until the Snow Melts"
Or you could just go to
the bookstore another day.
Is that you, Yoshikawa-san?
Yanagi-kun? Whoa, you're wearing glasses!
I thought it was you. What're you shopping for?
Oh, books and stuff, but mostly art supplies.
Art supplies? I didn't know you
were an artist, Yoshikawa-san.
Oh, they're not for me, they're for my sister...
"Stare"
This is my older sister.
Pleased to meet you, I'm Akane Yanagi.
Likewise. Didn't know Yuki was
friends with a hottie like you.
Unless you're her boyfriend?
No, ma'am. She turned me down.
I figured. You wouldn't date--
Wait, she turned you down?!
Not the other way around?!
Oh, my God, shut up!
Wait, hold on...
No, I'm far out of her league.
Wait, Yuki's league? This Yuki?
"You let this high-class meal go to waste?"
You can stop looking at me like that!
I hear you loud and clear!
"You let this high-class meal go to waste?"
Sorry, my sister's such an ass.
It's okay. This was a pleasant surprise.
I never imagined being able
to speak to you outside of school.
Oh, sorry, I shouldn't say that,
or Ishikawa-kun will get mad at me.
No, he wouldn't. You're a good guy, Yanagi-kun.
Toru wouldn't get mad.
I'm such a liar.
I hear those two are dating!
Wait, really? I thought so!
They are always together.
Yeah!
They make a good couple.
I know that Kono-san is totally fooled.
Fooled?
Kono-san thinks Toru and I are dating, right?
Does she? I have no idea.
She sorta asked me about it yesterday,
and I told her we were dating.
Why couldn't I just tell her the truth?
What's wrong with me?
Did you want to talk to me
to see if I'd tell her the truth?
Yeah.
I'll stay quiet about it if you admit
that you have a crush on Ishikawa-kun.
That's not fair.
What's not fair about it?
You're the one being unfair, don't you think?
She's right. This isn't fair to her.
I lied to Kono-san, knowing it would hurt her.
I'm...
I'd never seen someone's lips
tremble like that before.
Remi-chan, I...
The truth is...
Okay. Thanks, Yuki-chan.
I know this won't last forever.
I know Toru doesn't like me that way.
We should've stopped
pretending that very same day.
But he holds my hand.
He's nice to me, even when I don't deserve it.
If I asked you to keep up
the act for a while, would you?
Keep pretending, I mean.
Yeah, sure.
Maybe I just want this lie of ours
to become something real.
But...
That would never be okay.
Yuki was out today, too.
How many days is that now?
Three? Four? I think she's been out all week.
Maybe she's sick.
She'd text us back if she were sick.
Right, Toru?
Toru?
Oh, sorry, what's up?
Stop spacing out! We're talking about Yuki!
Have you gotten any texts
back from Yoshikawa-san?
Nope, she's not texting me, either.
Maybe she's dealing with family stuff.
Huh.
We should probably tell her the test
is gonna cover different stuff now.
Oh, good idea.
How funny would it be if she
threw a tantrum over the test stuff?
I dunno if she'd throw a whole tantrum.
I hope she comes tomorrow.
Yeah.
C'mon, you need to go to school already.
Aren't you worried about your attendance record?
Hello? I'm talking to you!
Ow!
This girl called Hori-san called.
She said you turned off your phone.
Lemme guess, you want something again, huh?
Any time you want something,
you never say you want it.
I have no idea why you do this.
There's nothing wrong or embarrassing
about wanting something.
But you need decide
if you're going to get it or not.
You always end up
complaining about it afterwards.
I want a hair clip like hers!
Yuki-chan, you just said you didn't want one!
Here, take it.
If you want something, then say so.
You've had this bad habit forever.
Hey, you stopped making those cookies, huh.
That last batch you did was pretty good.
Those pure-white ones, like snow--
like your name. Those were good.
Pure-white, like snow.
Like my name.
"12 New Messages"
"Hori: You're out again today. Sick?
Hope you're okay.
Most classes were self-study today.
Lemme know if you wanna see my notes though."
"Toru: You getting my texts?
You're not picking up your phone, either.
We're getting worried. At least text us!"
"Hori: I had Miyamura show me how to make
cookies today, but my batch came out awful.
He ate some anyways, but ended up
in the bathroom for an hour... I feel bad!"
"Toru: Kono-san told me she likes me."
Huh?
'Sup?
Yuki!
Yoshikawa's back.
Yeah. She looks good.
Oh, yeah, did I tell you the test's
covering different stuff now?
Yeah, I saw your text. This really sucks.
I guess it's still all stuff
I'm crap at, though.
Yoshikawa.
Can we talk?
Sure.
This is probably the end
of our little game of pretend.
What do you wanna talk about?
It's freezing up here; let's make it quick!
I gotta give Hori her notebook back, too.
Did you see my text?
Yeah, about Kono-san?
Yeah. When she told me she liked me...
She told me she didn't need an answer.
What?
Wait, she doesn't?!
Yeah.
For some reason she thinks we're dating,
so she just wanted to get that off her chest.
Why didn't you tell her, then?
That we're not dating?
I dunno. I didn't feel like I had
to clear up the misunderstanding.
Besides, I promised you I'd play along.
So if you didn't have to pretend,
what would you have told her?
Please, Kono-san's way out of my league.
I wouldn't be good for her.
She'll find someone way better than me.
O-Oh. Guess that means
no more sakura cookies, huh.
Yeah.
I totally thought he'd go for her,
what with how nice she is.
You haven't made me any of those
burned cookies lately, Yoshikawa.
O-Oh, shut up. I don't burn them anymore.
I'm a bad person.
Kono-san made him cookies every day,
worked up the courage to talk to him,
and told him how she felt,
even knowing she'd be rejected.
But all I do is run away.
I'm relieved that he's not going to date her,
but the possibility of him
not reciprocating my feelings
makes me too scared to breathe.
Even still, I...
I want to be the one at Toru's side.
I'm so selfish.
If she's warm Sakura cherry blossoms...
then I'm just gross, muddy,
freezing snow, just like my name.
I can see your breath.
I hear today's gonna be
the coldest day of the year.
If it's gonna be this cold,
it could at least snow.
We didn't get much snow last year.
I was looking forward to some this year.
Nobody wants it to snow.
You think so? It's so pretty, though.
Sure, it's pretty, but only in the beginning.
Shoveling it's a huge pain,
and you can slip and fall.
Yeah, I can see Miyamura slipping.
Yeah.
"FLOP"
And the gross muddy snow sticks
around for so long. Nobody likes that.
Everyone just waits for
it all to melt in the spring.
The snow doesn't melt just because it's spring.
Huh?
The snow melts because it
decides to melt on its own.
No matter how badly everyone
wants it to stick around,
the snow makes its own decision
to melt. That's why it melts.
You got that?!
I-It melts because it gets warmer.
So you think the snow melts
because the sakura blossoms ask it to?
What is this guy talking about?
Sounds like you need to go
back to first-grade science.
E-Excuse me?!
I can't believe he can say
all that with a straight face.
Still, it makes me happy.
You're so goddamn stupid, Toru.
Not as stupid as you, Yoshikawa.
That's the first time you've smiled all day.
How'd you know?
I just know.
It's freezing out here. Let's head in.
And whose bright idea was it
to come up here in the first place?
Yeah, I know.
Your hand's warm.
I really hope we get some snow!
The pure-white kind.
Huh? You think Sakura got a boyfriend?
Yeah, only because she
seems a lot happier as of late.
It's the exact opposite.
Huh?
Okay, I'm off to tutoring!
Okay, later.
Wait, what's the exact opposite
of getting a boyfriend?
Or was she talking about her not being happy?
Sengoku-kun?
Why are you cleaning?
The eraser bits on the floor were bothering me.
You should let the first-years
handle that! C'mon, now.
She's definitely in better spirits.
Almost like a weight's off her shoulders now.
And you should open the
window if you're going to clean.
Where's Remi?
She had tutoring today.
Remi always opens the window.
That's why I forgot. Thanks.
H-Hey, did something
change for you lately, Sakura?
You seem happier, but I don't think it's
because something good happened...
I mean, I hope it wasn't anything, but...
Sorry, I'm overthinking this, aren't I?
Sakura?
Huh? Oh, I'm heading home.
Sorry I can't help you clean.
Hold on, Sakura!
What... What happened?
Nothing happened.
I got rejected before I even
had a chance to ask him out.
That's it. That's all it is.
What a moron. He's got to be stupid.
Who's the idiot who didn't want to be with you?
He should be expelled for that.
Am I right?
Sakura--
That was the first time I ever saw
someone in my grade break down and sob.
It only hurts more because
nobody's in the wrong.
It started snowing.
"Next Time: It May Seem Like Hate"